usertube.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy

* * *

UserTube.com, being a portal site catering to India and India related topics, acts as conduit for a large amount of sensitive and private data. We use the information we collect from your requests to process orders of our services at present stage which are sharing time, feedback and future developments which includes email, homepages and etc.

Utmost care is taken to maintain the privacy of our visitors. It is our strict policy not to share, rent or sell such data to anyone under any circumstances. No specific information is used for any other purpose whatsoever.

It\'s important for us to have your correct email address when you send an inquiry, subscribe to newsletter and/or register for a survey in the database so that we can contact you and as certain the time of your visit to UserTube.

Please be advised that we NEVER update your information. Each time you send us any information, whether it\'s an inquiry, feedback, compliment, business related or general, we separate it from the last time so there is never a security concern. Also, we don\'t have any features to review your information such as, \"cookies\" or other fancy styles. Again, we respect your privacy and each email or details is done separately and one at a time.

Changes to this Privacy Policy

UserTube.com may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your mail subscribtion or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

UserTube.com contains many links to other sites. UserTube.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. UserTube.com does not share any of the individual personal information you provide with the sites to which UserTube.com links, although UserTube.com may share aggregate data with such sites (such as how many people use our site). This Includes other third party sites on the Internet for which UserTube.com provides search services. Please check with those sites to determine their privacy policy.

Questions and Suggestions

If you have questions or suggestions, please email us at:admin(at)UserTube.com
